We come
to you now with revelations
about last week's attack
in London.
An anonymous source
provided this video.
It shows Quentin Beck,
aka Mysterio,
moments before his death.
You may find
this video disturbing.
I managed to
send the Elemental back,
but I don't think I'm gonna
make it off this bridge.
Spider-Man attacked me.
He has an army of drones,
Stark technology.
He's saying he's gonna be
the new Iron Man. No one else.
Are you sure you want
to commence the drone attack?
There will be
significant casualties.
Do it. Execute them all.
This shocking video
was released earlier today
on the controversial
news website TheDailyBugle.net.
There you have it, folks.
Conclusive proof
that Spider-Man was responsible
for the brutal murder
of Mysterio,
an interdimensional warrior
who gave his life
to protect our planet
and who will, no doubt,
go down in history
as the greatest superhero
of all time.
But that's not all, folks.
Here's the real blockbuster.
Brace yourselves.
You might wanna sit down.
Spider-Man's real...
Spider-Man's real name is...
Spider-Man's name
is Peter Parker.
What the f...?
That's right, folks.
Peter Parker.
A 17-year-old
high school delinquent...
- She knows him.
- Are you Spider-Man's girlfriend?
...is, in fact...
Are you Spider-Man's
girlfriend?
...the vile vigilante villain
Spider-Man.
- Yo, it's him.
- Uh, whoa, whoa, whoa.
- Please don't touch her, sir.
- You're just a kid?
- You murdered Mysterio?
- Um...
- You helped him?
- No, I didn't...
Come on, kid,
let me see your face.
He hit me.
Spider-Man hit me!
- Come on.
- He hit me.
All this time,
people looked up to this boy
and called him a hero.
I'll tell you what I call him,
public enemy number one!
I told you I never wanted
to do this ever again!
MJ, I'm so sorry,
but I can't see anything
with your hand in my...
Sorry. Where are we
gonna go?
- I don't know. Your house?
- No! No!
My dad will kill you.
What? You said
your dad really liked me.
Yeah, well, not anymore.
Dude!
I'm so sorry.
Are you okay?
No, not really. Uh...
Yo, Peter!
We should go.
We should go. Come on.
- You said you don't want to swing.
- Swing me.
Okay. We can take the subway.
No.
Look out!
That was so much worse.
Okay. It's okay.
- Are you okay?
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Come on, come on, come on.
Okay, I'm so sorry.
Okay. Okay.
I'm sorry.
I just feel so dumb. I didn't
realize you were miserable.
No, it was really fun, right?
That's why they call it
a fling.
- And we flung.
- It was fun.
I could've been more fun.
- I can be fun.
- We'll hang out again.
Like, when do you think?
I should see what that is.
- No, no, no.
- It's what I do.
- He's always coming and going.
- Peter?
Oh, no.
- I don't know what to do.
- Peter. Peter.
- Oh, I...
- I didn't see anything.
This isn't what
it looks like.
- No, no, May.
- Practice safe...
Oh, hey. You must be MJ!
- Yeah. Nice to meet you.
- So nice to meet you.
Wait, have you
been crying?
We broke up.
- Hey, Spider-Man!
- Oh. Oh, uh...
Thank you. I didn't know
you broke up.
I thought you were
in love, May.
Can we talk about this
in the kitchen?
I should probably leave.
I thought you guys
were such a handsome couple.
It's really about boundaries.
- Let me answer the door.
- Let's go here.
- Is that the door?
- Hey. Is it true?
- I was gonna go, but...
- Not now.
I didn't know you were
so awkward about sex, Peter.
This has nothing to do
with sex.
If you wanna go over it again.
I mean... What's that sound?
- Hey, Spider-Man!
- Oh, my God.
I mean, I'm happy to rehash it
if you want to.
You take care of your
side, I'll take care of mine.
What is up
with this phone?
Will you get off your phones
for five minutes?
I just wanna talk to you
about your relationship, okay?
Peter?
What?
- Is that...?
- Is that here?
Um...
- Yo, Peter Parker!
- Yo, Peter!
Maybe it's not
such a big deal.
Spider-Menace!
Governments around the world
launch investigations
into the murderer
known as Spider-Man,
aka Peter Parker,
aka the web-headed
war criminal
who, for years,
has been terrorizing
the decent citizens
of New York.
Well, now this city
and the world
see him for what he truly is.
Murderer! Mysterio forever!
New details from last week's
devastating attack in London
have emerged.
For more, we go now to Joint
Intelligence headquarters.
Authorities
just a short while ago confirmed
that the deadly drones used
in the London attack
were designed
by Stark Industries.
Federal agents! Open up!
Federal agents? You stay here.
Department of Damage Control.
We have a warrant
for the arrest of Peter Parker.
- You know the Fourth Amendment?
- Sure.
Unreasonable search
and seizure?
Get in here, guys. Let's go.
I didn't kill Quentin Beck.
The drones did, okay?
- The drones that are yours.
- No.
Well, look. Nick Fury was there
the entire time.
Ask him.
He can explain everything.
Nick Fury has been off-planet
for the last year.
- What?
- Peter! Hey.
MJ! They have nothing
to do with this, sir.
Don't say anything
without a lawyer.
I want a lawyer.
- Ms. Jones-Watson.
- Jones. I don't go by Watson.
Ms. Jones, why do you
want a lawyer if...?
If I have nothing to hide?
Exactly. Unless...
- I'm actually guilty of something?
- Mm-hm.
I'm very aware of your tactics
and my rights.
Just answer my questions.
I've seen your file.
You're a smart young woman
with a bright future
ahead of her.
Why would you risk it all
by getting involved with
a vigilante like Peter Parker?
So sorry to keep you waiting.
- Can we get Ned a snack?
- Absolutely.
- He's been waiting.
- I got you.
Dude, I'm so sorry about that.
I'm not supposed
to say anything to you.
Not even a thing.
I just have one question.
When MJ told you
Peter was Spider-Man...
- Whoa, whoa, whoa. Heh.
- What's up?
I-I knew way before MJ did.
I was Spider-Man's
"guy in the chair."
I know about those.
Dude, half my guys
are guys in the chair.
Exactly. You would know.
I literally helped him
find the Vulture.
- I didn't know that.
- I helped him hack a suit once
and helped him get to space.
So in Spider-Man's
illegal vigilantism,
you were his main accomplice.
I would like to have my words
stricken from the record.
With all due respect, and
I mean that very insincerely,
unless you have some real
specific charges to throw at us,
legally, you can't hold us here.
- You should definitely lawyer up.
- Excuse me?
Child endangerment's
a nasty rap.
A boy was entrusted to you,
and as his legal guardian,
essentially his mother,
you not only allowed him
to endanger himself,
but you actually
encouraged it.
Who does that?
I wanna see Peter right now.
Stark
Industries was caught in the web
of the Spider-Man-Mysterio
controversy today,
when federal agents
opened an investigation
into missing Stark technology.
Agents wanna know
exactly what was taken...
At least they used
a good picture.
What is happening?
That's great. Thank you.
Well, I have
some good news, Peter.
I don't believe
any of the charges
- against you are gonna stick.
- Wait, seriously?
- I knew it.
- Nice.
My God, Mr. Murdock, thank you.
- Thank you, Matt.
- That's amazing.
- You're welcome.
- Perfect.
- However, Mr. Hogan.
- Yes?
The feds are investigating
that missing technology.
I understand your loyalty
to Mr. Stark and his legacy,
but if you were involved...
- If I was?
- I advise securing a lawyer.
I need a lawyer because I'm...?
I thought he was...
You said there's no charge.
I could say
under advisement of counsel,
I refuse to answer
the question respectfully
because the answer
can incriminate me...
It's in Goodfellas. What's the
thing they say in Goodfellas?
I know that's what you think.
Calm down.
Let's hear what
he has to say. Matt?
You're gonna need
a really good lawyer.
You may have dodged
your legal troubles
but things will get much worse.
There is still
the court of public opinion.
Murderer! Mysterio forever!
How did you just do that?
I'm a really good lawyer.
We're gonna need
a safer place to live.
Oh. Ah.
How do we...?
Alarm system deactivated.
It looks nice.
And this is safe.
Welcome to the spiritual oasis.
You like Donkey Kong Jr.?
Nicky from Jersey
City, you're on the line.
I'm not saying I don't
want to honor the Avengers,
but, you know,
not doing it this way.
Putting the
Captain America shield
on the Statue of Liberty?
Nah, that will look ridiculous.
Leave the Statue
of Liberty alone.
Oh, Happy.
Did you send in
your applications yet?
I just finished my MIT one.
- You?
- Same.
Can you imagine if
we both got in? And Ned?
Yeah, but we'd have
to get scholarships
so we could actually go.
You got the scores
and the grades.
You think I'm being
too pragmatic.
No, no, no. Well...
Kind of. It's okay.
It's one of my favorite
things about you.
- Really?
- Yeah.
What are your other
favorite things?
I love your
relentless optimism.
I am a glass-half-full
kind of gal.
I really like how
you're a people person.
I love people.
I love them so much.
You like sports.
I think the Mets are gonna
- go all the way this year.
- Really?
What's that noise?
Oh. It's Happy. Look.
Gave his room to May
so he's sleeping down here.
I have a weird question. Um...
Does any part of you
feel relieved about all of this?
Ever since I got bit
by that spider...
I've only had one week
where my life has felt normal.
Or kind of normal, I guess.
And...
that was when
you found out.
Because then everyone
that was in my life
that I wanted to know, knew.
And it was perfect.
But now everybody knows and...
I am the most famous person
in the entire world.
And I'm still broke.
I'm...
excited to see you tomorrow.
Yeah. Me too.
Wrap it up.
You both like each other.
We get it. Hang up.
There's no new ground being
broken. I need my eight hours.
Have you been listening
this whole time?
- Hi, Happy.
- Not by choice.
- MJ says hi.
- Hello.
We're covering
the first day of senior year
for Midtown High's
most famous student,
Peter Parker.
Go get them, tiger.
Or should I say "spider"?
The crowd has continued
to grow here all morning long
at the Midtown School
of Science...
The crowd seems evenly divided
between supporters
of Spider-Man
and protestors.
MJ! MJ! MJ! We love you!
MJ, are you gonna have
his spider-babies?
Back up. Back up. Back up!
MJ, you know
he's a murderer, right?
Peter. Do a TikTok with me.
- Mysterio forever!
- Do a flip!
- Hey, let's see you and MJ kiss!
- Back off.
Who are you?
Ned Leeds.
Spider-Man's best friend.
I'm Peter Parker's
best friend.
You come at my boy,
you come at Flash Thompson.
If you wanna read
about our inspiring friendship,
you can in my new book,
Flashpoint.
One spider, two hearts,
a million crazy-ass memories.
Check it out.
- Go.
- No, I gotta wait...
No. Go.
I'll see you inside, okay?
Keep watching Midtown News
all year
as we bring you up close
and personal coverage
of Peter fighting
his biggest battle yet,
college admissions.
Peter, we would love to welcome
you back to Midtown High,
where we shape heroes.
Yeah, uh-huh. Or murderers.
Stop it.
It's an honor
to serve you, sir.
It's not.
Mysterio was right.
- Stop. That's all.
- Mysterio was right.
Some of the students
put this together for you.
- No, you did that.
- I helped a little bit.
I tried to stop you so
many times but you powered through.
- He did all of that.
- Did a great job.
I hope you have time
to check it out.
Feel free to walk
or swing through the hallway.
Or crawl on the ceiling
to avoid everybody.
- We all know you can do it.
- I'm just gonna...
I know what you did.
Stop. You're
embarrassing yourself.
He's a conspiracy
theorist.
Can we just stay up here
all day?
- It is so crazy down there.
- This one's good.
"Some suggest
that Parker's powers
include the male spider's
ability to hypnotize females,
which he used to seduce
Jones-Watson
- into his cult of personality."
- Oh, come on. Stop. Stop.
Yes, my Spider-Lord.
Finally some privacy.
It is so crazy down there.
So I was thinking...
when we get into MIT,
we should live together.
- Yeah, for sure.
- Yeah, I'd love that.
- This is gonna be us.
- Yes.
Minus the Frisbee
and the smiling.
MIT's obviously the dream,
but if we match up
our backup schools,
then either way,
we'll be in Boston.
New school, new town.
I can Spider-Man there.
- They have crime in Boston, right?
- Yes.
- Wicked crime.
- It'll be like a fresh start.
What's up?
I don't know. I just feel
like, if you don't...
If you expect disappointment,
then you can never really
get disappointed.
Come on.
Be a fresh start.
And we'll all be together.
Yeah. No, you're right.
Fresh start.
Yeah.
First one's here!
It's okay.
It's a backup school.
Peter!
No?
Last one.
MIT?
Uh... Okay.
Okay.
- Phew.
- Ready?
Jones. I told you to take down
the Halloween decorations.
Actually, that was Sasha so...
Enough attitude.
Just do it.
On it.
Feel like I'm gonna puke.
Don't, because he will
just make me clean it.
This is our only shot.
It's here or nowhere.
- Hey. Come on.
- Okay. You guys ready?
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- Okay, on three.
One, two, three.
No.
You?
"In light of recent controversy,
we are unable to consider
your application at this time."
This is so not fair.
I mean, this is so not fair.
I didn't do anything wrong.
You guys definitely
didn't do anything wrong.
Expect disappointment and
you will never get disappointed.
♪ No sleep till ♪
♪ Boston ♪
You guys didn't get in?
Yeah, because we're actually
friends with Spider-Man.
Uh, yeah. I better get going.
There's a mixer
for new admissions and...
Sorry, guys.
Jones, what are you doing?
Get back to work.
Yeah, I'm coming.
Know what?
I wouldn't change
a thing I did.
Me neither.
Although I do need to show
this letter to my parents.
Um, hi.
Hi?
I'm, uh...
The most famous person
in the world.
I know.
Wong. Try not to slip.
We don't have
liability insurance.
Is all this
for a holiday party?
No. One of the rotunda
gateways connects to Siberia.
A blizzard blasted through.
Because someone forgot to cast
a monthly maintenance spell
to keep the seals tight.
That's right, he did,
because he forgot
- I now have higher duties.
- Higher duties?
The Sorcerer Supreme
has higher duties. Yes.
Wait, I thought you were
the Sorcerer Supreme.
No, he got it
on a technicality
because I blipped
for five years.
- Oh, well, congratulations.
- If I'd been here, then...
You'd burn the place down.
You two, no one said
stop shoveling.
So, Peter, to what
do I owe the pleasure?
Right. I'm really sorry
to bother you, sir.
Please. We saved half
the universe together.
Think we're beyond
you calling me "sir."
Okay, uh, Stephen.
That feels weird,
but I'll allow it.
When...
When Mysterio
revealed my identity...
my entire life got screwed up
and I was wondering...
I don't know
if this would actually work,
but I was wondering if...
maybe you could go back in time
and make it so he never did?
Peter...
we tampered with the stability
of space-time
to resurrect countless lives.
You wanna do it again now
because yours got messy?
It's not about me.
I mean, this is really hurting
a lot of people.
My Aunt May, Happy,
my best friend,
my girlfriend,
their futures are ruined
just because they know me,
and they've done
nothing wrong.
I am so sorry...
but even if I wanted to...
I don't have
the Time Stone anymore.
That's right.
I'm really sorry
if I wasted your time.
- No. You didn't.
- Just forget about it.
He will. He's very good
at forgetting things.
Wong, you've actually
generated a good idea.
What?
The Runes of Kof-Kol.
The Runes of Kof-Kol?
It's just a standard
spell of forgetting.
Won't turn back time,
but people will forget
you were ever Spider-Man.
- Seriously?
- No, not seriously.
That spell travels
the dark borders
between known
and unknown reality.
It's too dangerous.
We've used it for a lot less.
Do you remember the full moon
party at Kamar-Taj?
- No.
- Exactly.
Come on, Wong.
Hasn't he been through enough?
Just leave me out of this.
Fine.
So, what is this place?
The Sanctum's built
at the intersection
of cosmic energy currents.
We weren't the first
to seek them out.
Some of these walls
are thousands of years old.
And they shot an episode of
The Equalizer here in the '80s.
Well, I, um...
really appreciate you
doing this for me, sir.
Don't mention it.
And don't call me "sir."
Right. Sorry.
You ready?
I'm ready.
Nice knowing you, Spider-Man.
Wait, excuse me?
The entire world's
about to forget
that Peter Parker
is Spider-Man.
- Including me.
- Everyone?
Uh, can't some people
still know?
That's not how
the spell works.
And it's very difficult
and dangerous
to change it mid-casting.
So my girlfriend's
gonna forget everything?
Is she even gonna be
my girlfriend?
Was she your girlfriend
because you were Spider-Man?
- I don't know. I really hope not.
- All right, fine.
Everyone in the world's
gonna forget you're Spider-Man
except your girlfriend.
Thank you so much.
Oh, my God, Ned. Ned.
What is a Ned?
He's my best friend
so it's important to me
that Ned knows.
Okay, let's not change
the parameters of this spell
any more
while I'm casting it.
Okay, I'm done.
I swear I'm done. I'm done.
But my Aunt May
should really know.
Peter, stop tampering
with the spell.
When she found out,
it was really messy.
I don't think
I could go through that again.
- So my Aunt May?
- Yes.
Thank you. Happy?
No, I'm annoyed.
No, it's a nickname.
Harold "Happy" Hogan.
He used to work with Tony Stark,
but then he was...
Could you just stop talking?
Basically everyone that knew
I was Spider-Man before
should still know!
- Did it work?
- No.
You changed my spell six times.
- Five times.
- You changed my spell.
You don't do that. I told you.
And that is why.
That spell was out of control.
If I hadn't shut it down,
something catastrophic
could have happened.
- Stephen, listen, I am so...
- Call me "sir."
Sorry, sir.
After everything
we've been through,
somehow I always forget
you're just a kid.
Look, Parker, the problem
is not Mysterio.
It's you trying to live
two different lives.
And the longer you do that,
the more dangerous it becomes.
Believe me. I'm so sorry
about you and your friends
not getting into college,
but if they rejected you
and you tried
to convince them to reconsider,
there's nothing else
you can do.
When you say, "Convince them,"
- you mean I could have called them?
- Yeah.
I could do that?
You haven't called the...?
I got their letter.
I assumed that was...
I'm sorry.
Are you telling me
that you didn't even think to
plead your case with them first
before you asked me
to brainwash the entire world?
Well, I mean,
when you put it like that...
Come on, pick up, pick up.
Dude, what? I'm busy.
- Flash, where's the MIT mixer?
- Why?
Because I need
to talk to someone.
I'm trying to get Ned and MJ
a second chance at getting in.
What's in it for me?
I'm risking a lot
just talking to you.
Okay, I will, um...
pick you up and swing you
to school for one week?
For a month.
- For a week.
- Two weeks.
- Flash, please. Help me.
- You know what I want.
Okay, I'll tell everyone
you're my best friend.
- Flash, please help me.
- Cool, cool, cool.
There's the
assistant vice chancellor.
You can plead your case
with her.
- Perfect. Where is she?
- She left.
- To go where?
- To the airport.
Stark network unavailable.
Facial recognition unavailable.
Hi.
Yeah, I can see you.
Oh, my God.
- That's Peter Parker.
- Mom.
- Mom, look.
- Mommy.
No, it's Peter Parker.
Hey.
Okay.
Whew.
- Yeah.
- Hi. I'm Peter Parker.
You do know you're
in the street, right?
Yeah, I'm sorry. I really
needed to talk to you
and I know you're
on your way to the airport.
MJ Watson and Ned Leeds are the
two smartest people I've met,
and I'm the dumbest person
because I let them help me,
but if I didn't,
millions would've died,
so please don't let MIT
be dumb like me.
MIT is dumb?
No, I'm saying
don't let MIT be dumb.
I mean, like
the dumber version of me
that wouldn't have
let them help.
You didn't rehearse that,
did you, Peter?
Basically, what I'm trying to...
Why are you running?
Oh, my God.
Ma'am, you should get out
of the car.
Everybody get off the bridge!
The door's locked.
Door's... Hey!
Hello, Peter.
Hi? Do we...? Do I know you?
What have you done
with my machine?
I don't know what you're
talking about. What machine?
The power of the sun
in the palm of my hand.
It's gone.
Listen, sir,
if you stop smashing cars,
we can work together and I can
help you find your machine.
You want to play games?
Catch.
It's okay. You guys are good.
You're safe. Get out.
You think your fancy new suit's
gonna save you?
Should've killed
your little girlfriend
when I had the chance.
What did you just say?
Looks like we got competition.
Peter! Help!
Don't worry, ma'am! I'm coming!
Peter!
Ma'am, just stay calm.
Just take
a deep breath.
- Are you okay?
- No!
I promise, I've got this
all under control.
Suit compromised.
Nanotechnology.
Ah, you've outdone yourself,
Peter.
I underestimated you.
But now you die.
You're not Peter Parker.
I am so confused right now.
What's happening?
New device detected.
Pairing new device.
You don't listen to him.
You listen to me.
Hey.
Whoa.
Hey. Hey!
Listen to me.
No, not him.
Me.
Ma'am, you okay?
Come on, you can still
make your flight.
Peter.
You're a hero.
No. Well, I'm... No, I'm...
I'm gonna talk to Admissions
about your friends.
And I'm gonna talk
to them about you.
But, ma'am,
this isn't about me.
I am going to talk to them
about your friends and you.
- Okay?
- Really?
And if you keep
your noses clean,
maybe you'll have a fair shot.
Here. Get out of the way.
Let me get that man.
Hey! You! I see you.
Come here!
That was not okay.
Unbelievable.
Who are...?
Hey. Hey, hey, hey.
Until you stop
trying to kill me,
I'm in control, buddy,
of this whole
tentacle situation
you got going on here,
okay?
Now, who are you?
What is going...?
No.
Osborn?
Doctor...?
Be careful
what you wish for, Parker.
Let me out of here!
Can you please explain to me
what is going on?
That little spell
that you botched
where you wanted
everyone to forget
that Peter Parker's
Spider-Man,
it started pulling in
everyone
who knows
Peter Parker's Spider-Man
from every universe
into this one.
- From every universe?
- Who are you? And where am I?
I think it's
better we don't engage
with them because,
frankly,
the multiverse
is a concept about which
we know frighteningly little.
The multiverse is real?
This shouldn't even be possible.
- I thought you stopped the spell.
- No, I contained it.
It would appear
a few of them squeaked through.
After you left, I detected
an otherworldly presence.
I pursued it into the sewers,
where I found that...
slimy green son of a gun.
Spell? As in magic?
What is this,
a birthday party?
Who is this clown?
What is this madness?
Watch this.
Do you know a Peter Parker
- who's Spider-Man?
- Yes.
- Is that him?
- No.
See?
Okay, here's what we gotta do.
I don't know how many
visitors we've got...
I saw another one
on the bridge.
He was like a
flying green elf.
He sounds jolly.
Start with him.
I need you
to capture them,
bring them here
while I figure out
how to get them back
before
they destroy
the fabric of reality,
or worse, Wong finds out.
Uh, Doctor Strange?
What?
My friends and I just got a
second chance to get into MIT,
and if the school sees me
fighting these crazy monsters...
- Hey, watch your mouth.
- I'm sorry but...
Are you seriously
still talking about college?
- Hey, what did you just do?
- This.
Hey, you can't just...
How did you do that?
Lots of birthday parties.
Hey.
Whoa.
One shot,
send them here, move on.
You're welcome. Get to work.
Sir?
Now what?
I know this is my mess,
and I swear to you I'll fix it,
but I'm gonna need help.
Whoa!
I can't believe
I'm in the Sanctum Sanctorum.
Neither can I.
So how did you know
you were a man of magic?
Because my nana says
that we have it in our family,
and I get these tinglings
in my hands...
Talk to your physician.
- Peter.
- Hey.
- Hey. Hey.
Sorry for dragging you
into this.
- Help me find these guys.
- You don't have to apologize.
You got us a second shot
at MIT. It's fine.
So how did the bad guys
get here?
We screwed up a spell
trying to get you into college.
- Wait. What?
- You did it with magic?
I thought it was
the MIT lady you saved.
No, that was after.
Let's just focus
on the good news, okay?
No, let's just focus
on the bad news.
As of now, you have detected
zero multiversal trespassers,
so get on your phones,
scour the Internet, and...
Scooby-Doo this shit.
You're telling us
what to do even though
it was your spell
that got screwed up,
meaning that all this
is kind of your mess.
I know a couple of
magic words myself,
starting with
the word "please."
Please Scooby-Doo this shit.
You can work in the undercroft.
The undercroft?
Badass.
- About this whole spell thing...
- It's totally okay.
- Wait, really?
- Yeah. I mean, I get it.
You were just trying
to fix things, and so...
Maybe just run it by us
next time, you know?
That way, when you're thinking,
"I'm about to do something
that could break the universe,"
we could, like, help you
workshop something or...
brainstorm ideas.
Deal.
Ned?
Oh, dude, I don't care.
It's seriously not a big deal.
Um, oh!
A torture rack.
That is a Pilates machine.
- That is...
- The crypt.
Okay, so we get
the rest of the guys,
you zap them, Doctor Magic
will send them back,
and when we get into MIT,
round of stale doughnuts,
my treat.
Let's catch
some multiverse men.
Hey! Who the hell
are these two?
- My friends. This is MJ.
- Hey.
- And this is Ned.
- Hello.
Uh, I'm sorry,
what was your name again?
Dr. Otto Octavius.
Wait, no, seriously,
what's your actual name?
Oh, is that
a dinosaur?
If the paint
won't come off, I'll get it out.
No, no, no. May. We gotta
find these guys first.
Well, finish your mission,
and then come by.
We're having
a canned food drive.
- That could work.
- I got one.
- May, I gotta go.
- Okay.
I mean, you can take
the guy out of the chair,
but you can't take
the chair out of the guy.
- What'd you find?
- There's a...
A disturbance near
a military research facility
outside of the city,
and witnesses say
that they saw
a monster flying
through the air.
It's gotta be the guy
I saw on the bridge, right?
That's impossible.
You know him, don't you?
On the bridge,
you said his name.
Norman Osborn.
Brilliant scientist.
Military research.
But he was greedy, misguided.
- What happened to him?
- We tire of your questions, boy!
Okay, um...
I gotta go. Where am I going?
It can't be him.
Why?
Because Norman Osborn
died years ago.
So either we saw someone else...
or you're flying out into
the darkness to fight a ghost.
Keep an eye out on the trees.
We don't know where this guy is.
I genuinely don't know how you
do this without throwing up.
Did you guys see that?
Um, no.
It's-It's really dark.
Okay, okay, okay, okay.
What-What's happening?
Peter, what is it?
Are you getting
the tingle thing?
Is the tingle happening?
Is your tingle tingling?
- Are you guys seeing this?
- Yeah.
Osborn?
No. He was green.
This guy's blue.
You wouldn't happen to be from
another universe, would you?
What's he doing?
I don't know.
Looks like he's charging.
I don't like this.
Just web him.
Whoa!
Go left! Left, dude, left!
Left! Go! Left! Yes!
What are you talking about?
Right.
Go to the right! Right!
Right! He means right.
- Don't listen to him.
- Guys, this is not helping!
Oh, no, no, no.
What happened? Peter? Peter.
Whoa.
Peter, it's me, Flint Marko.
You remember?
I'm Peter,
but I'm not your Peter.
What do you mean,
you're not my Peter?
What the hell is going on?
I'll explain, but first,
can you help me?
- Okay.
- You try to surround him,
and I'll pull the plug.
All right, let's go!
I can't hold him much longer.
I got it, I got it!
Different Peter. Weird.
- Thanks. Sorry.
- Don't worry about it.
I got my body back.
Hey, um...
This is gonna sound
really crazy,
but this isn't your universe.
Another universe?
- Uh-huh.
- What?
That's what I was feeling.
The power, it's different.
I like it.
Easy, buddy.
It's actually my fault
that you're here.
Like, the universe or the woods?
I hate the woods.
I meant the universe, sir.
So, what, y'all
just gonna stand here
and act like I ain't
butt-ass naked?
- I am.
- No, no.
I, uh...
What was that?
What did you just do to him?
- No. It's okay.
- Did you kill him?
I can explain everything.
Trust me.
Please just trust me.
I don't trust you.
I don't know you.
What is this?
You picked the wrong side.
Connors?
Wait. You know this creature?
No, no, no.
Not a creature. A man.
The same universes.
Dr. Curt Connors.
He was a scientist
at Oscorp when I worked there.
A brilliant scientist.
Until he turned himself
into a lizard.
Then he tried to turn
the whole city into lizards.
- It was crazy.
- It wasn't crazy, Max.
It was the next step
in human evolution.
- The dinosaur can talk. Right.
- Lizard.
Speaking of which
what happened to you?
Last I recall,
you had bad teeth,
glasses and a comb-over.
Did you get a makeover?
You know I can give you
a real makeover.
Let me guess, into a lizard?
- Exactly.
- Would you two just shut up?
- Where are we?
- It's complicated.
- A wizard's dungeon.
- Wizard's dungeon?
There's no real way
to sugarcoat that.
It's literally the dungeon
of a wizard.
You can keep your magic.
I want a taste of that
new energy I just felt.
- Oh, Peter, hey.
- Did those guys come through yet?
There should be
an electric guy and a sand guy.
Yeah, they're all here
and locked up.
Perfect. I'm gonna just
stay here for a bit
and try and fix
some of this damage
so they don't blame it
on me again.
- Okay.
- But, hey, I, uh...
I couldn't do any of this
without you, so thank you.
Yeah, of course.
Hey, ask him if this is,
like, a tree monster
or, like,
a scientist
that turned into a tree.
It's just a tree, man.
Just a tree.
Coward.
We have a new world to conquer.
You make me sick.
Leave me alone, please.
Hiding in the shadows.
Hiding from who you truly are.
- No.
- You can't escape yourself.
- Hey, May.
- Hey, Peter. I'm at work, and...
one of the guys you're
looking for just walked in.
May? Where's May?
Thank you.
May.
Ah, hey, here he is.
Norman, this is my nephew.
Norman Osborn?
I thought that you were...
I saw Spider-Man
in an ad for this place.
And I thought
he could help me.
But you're not him.
Wait, so you want
Spider-Man's help?
He just wandered in.
I didn't know
where else to go.
Someone's living in my house.
Oscorp doesn't exist.
My son...
Sometimes I'm not myself.
I'm someone else.
- Mm-hm.
- And every time he's in control,
- I can't remember.
- Who? Who's in control?
- And now I'm here...
- Who's in control?
- I don't know what's going on.
- Okay, it's okay.
And I don't...
Doesn't make sense.
He's lost.
And I don't mean just in
the cosmos. I mean in his mind.
Are they all like this?
- Yeah.
- Yeah?
They all have their own
mental or physical issues.
Oh, well, he needs help
and maybe they all do.
Wait, you don't mean...?
No, May, this isn't my problem.
Peter, not your problem? Hmm?
May. Their chance
of getting help is way better
back where they came from.
Sending them home,
that's the best thing
we can do for them.
For them? Or for yourself?
Look around you.
This is what we do.
- We help people.
- This is what's best for them.
Trust me.
But the fact remains,
Spider-Man is a menace.
We'll be right back
after a brief word
from Daily Bugle Supplements.
The only other daily fix
you need.
And we're out.
What?
I got eyes on him.
He's with his aunt
and some guy.
- You sure?
- They're leaving the shelter.
Okay. Don't lose him.
Thanks, May.
Hope to see you again.
Hey. He trusts you. So do I.
Thanks for cleaning my suit.
I'll see you later.
- Um, guys, this is Mr. Osborn.
- Hey, it's "doctor."
Sorry. Um, Dr. Osborn,
these are my friends.
This is Ned and MJ.
- Mary Jane?
- It's Michelle Jones, actually.
Fascinating.
Do you think
there are other Ned Leedses?
Octavius?
Osborn?
- What... What happened to you?
- What happened to...?
- You're the walking corpse.
- What do you mean?
You died, Norman.
Years ago.
You're insane.
- God, I love it here.
- What are you talking about?
He's standing right there.
He's not...
Dead. They both died,
fighting Spider-Man.
It was all over the news.
Green Goblin, impaled by
the glider you flew around on.
And a couple of years later,
you, Doc Ock,
drowned in the river
with your machine.
That's nonsense.
Spider-Man was trying
to stop my fusion reactor,
so I stopped him.
I had him by the throat,
and then I...
- And then I was here.
- Ah, please.
Let me tell you something.
I was whupping Spider-Man's ass.
He'll tell you.
And then he caused an overload.
I was stuck in the grid,
absorbing data.
I was about to turn
into pure energy, and then...
And then, uh...
And then... Oh, shit.
- I was about to die.
- Max, do you know? Do I die?
Oh, great.
You caught another one.
No, wait, Strange.
He's not dangerous.
It's okay. Um...
What is that?
It's an ancient relic.
The Macchina di Kadavus.
I trapped
your corrupted spell inside,
and once I finish
the proper ritual,
it'll reverse the spell
and send these guys
back to their universes.
And then what? We perish?
No. No, thanks.
I'll pass on that.
Let me out of here. Peter!
Strange, we can't
send them back. Not yet.
Why?
Well, some of these guys
are gonna die.
Parker, it's their fate.
Come on, Strange, have a heart.
In the grand calculus
of the multiverse,
their sacrifice means infinitely
more than their lives.
I'm sorry, kid.
If they die, they die.
Peter!
Don't.
- Dude, what are you doing?
- Peter, you gotta go. Go, go.
- Okay.
- Get out of here.
This is why I never had kids.
- Give me the box.
- No.
Whoa!
- Oh, my God, I'm dead.
- You're not dead,
you've just been separated
from your physical form.
My physical... What?
- How are you doing that?
- I have no idea.
You should not
be able to do that.
This feels amazing.
That's one of the coolest
things that's happened to me,
but don't ever do that again.
Wha... Hey! Get off of me!
♪ La, la ♪
♪ Tis the season
To be jolly... ♪
- What is this place?
- The Mirror Dimension,
where I'm in control.
Strange, stop. Can we
please just talk about this?
Parker, don't you realize
that in the multiverse
there are an infinite number
of people
who know Peter Parker
is Spider-Man?
And if that spell gets loose,
they're all coming here.
I know, I get it, but we can't
just send them home to die.
It's their fate.
You can't change that
any more than you could
change who they are.
But what if we could? What if
we could change their fate?
Whoa! Oh, what are you doing?
I'm not giving you the... Whoa!
Whoa! Whoa!
Give me that back.
Wait a minute.
Is that an Archimedean Spiral?
The Mirror Dimension
is just geometry?
You're great at geometry.
You can do geometry.
Square the radius.
Divide by pi.
- Plot points along the curve.
- It's over, Parker.
I'll come pick you up
when it's done.
Hey, Strange.
You know
what's cooler than magic?
- Math.
- Don't do this.
- Ow.
- I'm sorry, sir, but...
...I have to try.
- What happened?
- I fought with Strange and won.
- What?
- Look, I stole his ring thing.
I was swinging through the city,
and then I went through
this massive mirror thing,
and then I was back in...
- Where is he?
- He's trapped,
- but I'm not sure for how long.
- You could have left us to die.
Why didn't you?
Because that's not who he is.
I think I can help you guys.
If I can fix what happened
to you, then when you go back,
things will be different,
and you might not die
fighting Spider-Man.
- What do you mean fix us?
- Our technology is advanced...
I can help you. You know, I'm
something of a scientist myself.
Octavius knows what I can do.
Fix? You mean like a dog?
I refuse.
I can't promise
you guys anything,
but at least this way, you get
to go home and have a chance.
A second chance.
Come on,
isn't that worth trying?
Trust me, Peter,
when you try to fix people,
there are always consequences.
I mean, you don't have to come.
I also didn't know
that you could talk.
But if you stay here,
you're gonna have to deal
with the wizard.
Ah, so we go along or die.
Not much of a choice, is it?
- I just wanna go home.
- Well, I, myself,
don't wanna be killed,
especially by a guy dressed
like Dungeons and Dragons,
so, what's your plan?
I have it all under control.
What are we
gonna do about this thing?
Uh, well, we need to find
somewhere safe for it, right?
- Yeah, sure. You gotta take it.
- Wait, what?
If something bad happens,
you just push this,
- and then it's all over.
- We're not gonna leave you.
You can't. It's dangerous.
You've done enough.
- We're in this together.
- I know we're in this together,
but I can't do this
if you're in danger.
Okay? So for me, MJ,
please just take this.
- Please.
- Fine.
- Thank you.
- But, Peter,
if I don't hear from you,
I'm pressing the button.
- Sure.
- Okay. And I will do it.
Yeah, we all believe you,
Michelle.
No way that's his girlfriend.
No way.
- She'll do it.
- Absolutely, she will.
- Okay. See you later.
- Be safe.
- You too.
- Okay.
Whoa.
Okay.
- Be careful, okay?
- Yeah. You too.
So, uh...
who's coming with me?
Well, I'm in.
But if this goes sideways...
I'm gonna fry you
from the inside out.
Where's Connors?
He wants to stay in the truck.
Okay.
Alarm system deactivated.
Hey, May.
- Yeah?
- I feel kind of bad
- using Happy's place like this.
- No, no, no. He'll get over it.
New Yorkers
- oppose the renovation...
- Oh, sorry.
So this is your plan, Peter, hm?
No lab, no facilities?
Just performing miracles
in a condominium, hm?
What, you gonna cook us
some cures
and some frozen burritos
in a microwave?
- I could go for a burrito.
- He's gonna kill us all.
Well, let's hope not.
- You're up first, Doc.
- What?
Hey, I told you,
I don't need fixing.
Especially by a teenager
using scraps
from a bachelor's junk drawer.
Nah, nah, nah.
He got something back there.
I can feel it.
That weird energy.
What the hell is that?
It's a fabricator.
It can analyze, design,
construct basically anything.
I thought that was
the tanning bed Happy broke.
Look at that.
He's gonna kill us all.
Whoa. What's going on there?
So the chip in
the back of Doc's neck
was designed to protect
his brain from the AI system
that's controlling
these tentacles,
but if you look here...
the chip is fried.
So rather than him being
in control of the tentacles,
the tentacles are now
in control of him.
Which, I guess, explains why
he is so miserable all the time.
Thirsty?
Well, yes, I am thirsty.
Fresh water or salt?
You know,
because you're an octopus.
What?
Fresh water it is.
Look at this place.
- And all the possibilities.
- What, this condo?
Yeah, yeah, the condo. I love
the whole open floor plan. No.
No, man,
I'm talking about the world.
I kind of like who I am here.
And all that power back there...
I could be so much more.
So why'd you come along?
I have a daughter,
and I want to see her.
But he's not gonna
send anyone home
till he's finished his little
science project back there.
You trust him?
I don't trust anyone.
How'd you end up
like that anyway?
Oh...
the place where I worked at,
they were experimenting
with electricity
created by living organisms,
and then, uh...
I fell into
a vat of electric eels.
You're kidding.
I fell into a supercollider.
Damn.
Gotta be careful
where you fall.
Remarkable.
The technology and you.
When all this is over,
if you need a job
and you're willing to commute
to another universe...
It worked. That totally worked.
I got it. I did it.
Uh, will you send him up?
Here we go.
- Sorry.
- Hold on, Doc.
Oh, will these humiliations
never cease?
You, keep your science fair
project away from me!
It'll work. Have faith.
Says the reckless fool who
turned himself into a monster.
Please stop moving your head.
- Hold still.
- Don't you dare.
Ugh! I swear,
when I get out of this,
we're gonna rip you a new...
Doc?
Dr. Octav...
It's so quiet.
Those voices inside my head...
I'd almost forgotten.
Otto.
Yes. Norman.
It's me.
Would you look at that.
I'm grateful, dear boy. Truly.
Yeah, you're welcome.
How can I help?
This is Peter. Leave a message.
Uh, yeah, Peter, this is Happy.
I accessed my doorbell camera.
Who are those guys, huh?
Is that a cyborg?
You bring a cyborg
with robot legs into my house?
Was one of the guys made of mud?
What's going on? Call me.
How does it feel, Norman?
You're about
to become whole again.
No more darker half.
Just you.
Just me.
Okay, um...
It just goes right here. This...
That should be
drawing power now.
I'm gonna come back
in a second to check,
but keep an eye on the lights.
When they're all green,
it means the electricity
in your body's dissipated.
Well, not all
of the electricity.
You need electricity
for your brain to function.
Your nervous system is...
I'm not really sure why I'm
explaining electricity to you.
- Yeah, can I ask you a question?
- Sure.
Are these your Legos?
Uh, I gotta go. I'll be back.
- Something feels off.
- What do you mean?
- I don't like this.
- Leave it alone.
The sooner you guys get through
this, the sooner we go home.
- Well, where is he?
- Uh, he's inside.
And yet here we are, outside.
Did you not hear me say,
"Don't lose him?"
I want incriminating footage
of Spider-Man.
I called Damage Control.
They're on their way.
And so it begins.
...place is about
to be swarming with cops.
Peter?
What's wrong?
I don't know.
May?
What is it, Peter?
What's happening?
Why are you
looking at me like that?
That's some neat trick,
that sense of yours.
- Norman?
- Norman's on sabbatical, honey.
- The hell?
- The Goblin.
"No more darker half"?
Did you really think
that I'd let that happen?
That I'd let you take away my
power just because you're blind
to what true power
can bring you?
- You don't know me.
- Don't I?
I saw how she trapped you,
fighting her holy moral mission.
We don't need you to save us.
We don't need to be fixed.
These are not curses.
They're gifts.
- Norman, no.
- Quiet, lapdog.
You don't know
what you're talking about.
I've watched you from deep
behind Norman's cowardly eyes.
Struggling to have
everything you want
while the world tries
to make you choose.
Gods don't have to choose.
We take.
May, run.
Oh, my God.
- What have you done?
- I liked you better before.
Up here. He's up there.
It's the guy from the bridge.
Did you see that?
No, you don't!
Strong enough to have it all.
Too weak to take it!
Now I got you.
I told you
there'd be consequences.
Your weakness, Peter,
is morality.
It's choking you.
Can't you feel it?
It didn't work.
Norman was right.
He got it from you,
that pathetic sickness.
You tried to fix me.
- May, go.
- Now I'm gonna fix you.
May, run, please.
May!
Peter, Peter, Peter.
No good deed goes unpunished.
You can thank me later.
No!
- May?
- Peter.
May, May, I'm here.
Oh!
- May.
- Oh!
May, I'm here.
- Are you okay?
- Uh-huh, uh-huh.
What happened?
Okay... Oh!
It's okay. We're okay, right?
Yeah. Knocked on my ass.
- Yeah, me too.
- That's all.
I think I broke my ribs.
- This is all my fault, May.
- No.
I should have let Strange
send them back.
You did the right thing.
They would have been killed.
It's not my responsibility, May.
Oh. What Norman said?
My moral mission? No.
- No, May...
- Peter, you listen to me.
You have a gift.
You have power.
And with great power,
there must also come
great responsibility, mm?
Yeah, I know.
Let's get the... out of here.
Okay, let's go.
Let me just catch my...
- What happened? Are you okay?
- I'm okay.
Yeah, you're okay.
What happened?
Just have to...
- catch my breath.
- Okay, well, catch your breath.
I'm right here.
We're gonna take our time.
You catch your breath.
Then we'll take you
to a doctor, okay?
Are you okay?
Somebody help! I need
an ambulance, please! Somebody?
- What happened?
- Nothing happened.
You're okay, you're okay.
Let me just...
Let me catch my breath.
I'm right here. I'm right here.
I'm right here.
You're okay.
It's just me and you.
May?
Will you look at me,
May, please?
May.
What are you doing, May?
Please, will you just wake up
and talk to me? Please?
Get out of the car now! Move!
Get off, get off, get off me.
- Peter! Run!
- It's just me and you, okay?
It's just me and you, okay?
Oh, May, I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
I'm so, so, so sorry.
I love you.
All right, Parker!
Come out with your hands up!
Come out right
now, or we will open fire!
Run!
All right, let's go.
Let's go! Move in!
Tragedy.
What else can I call it?
What more need be said?
The damage, the destruction.
You saw it with your own eyes.
When will people wake up
and realize
that everywhere
Spider-Man goes,
chaos and calamity ensue?
Everything Spider-Man touches
comes to ruin.
And we, the innocents,
are left to pick up the pieces.
J. Jonah Jameson reporting.
Good night,
and God help us all.
We are told that multiple
people have been injured,
and we can confirm at least
one person has been killed...
Still nothing?
No.
I'm gonna press it.
- What? No, he...
- I know he told me to wait...
- but I'm gonna do it.
- I just wish...
I just wish we could see him.
- Ned?
- Yeah?
- Do that again.
- Yeah.
I just wish we could see him.
Oh. Okay.
I just wish we could see Peter.
Whoa.
Lola, you're right. I am magic.
Is that him?
- Yeah, yeah, it has to be.
- Peter. Peter!
- Hey, Peter!
- Peter!
Yeah.
Whoa!
Hi. Hi.
No, no, no, it's okay.
It's okay. I'm a nice guy.
Okay.
- Who the hell are you?
- I'm Peter Parker.
- That's not possible.
- I am Spider-Man, in my world.
But then yesterday, I was...
I was just here.
Wow.
String theory,
multi-dimensional reality...
and matter displacement.
- All real?
- Yeah.
I knew it.
This has to be
because of the spell.
The spell? Like magic spell?
- There's no spell. No.
- No spell.
- Magic's real here too?
- I mean...
- Shut up, Ned.
- No, it's not real.
- Shut up. Stop talking.
- There's magicians, but no...
Stop. Stop.
- Prove it.
- Prove what?
- That you're Peter Parker.
- I don't carry
an ID with me, you know?
Kind of defeats the whole
anonymous superhero thing.
- Why'd you do that?
- To see if you have the tingle.
I have the tingle thing,
just not for bread.
Can you not
throw the bread again?
You're a deeply
mistrusting person...
and I respect it.
Crawl around.
- Crawl around?
- Yes.
- No.
- Yes, crawl around.
- Why do I need to?
- This is not enough.
- This is plenty.
- No, it's not.
- Yes, it is. It is.
- No, it's not. Nuh-uh.
- How do I stick to the ceiling?
- Do it.
Ned.
My lola's asking
if you could just
get the cobweb there.
- Since you're, like, up there.
- Yeah.
Thank you.
We goo...?
- We good?
- For now.
So I opened the wrong portal
to the wrong Peter Parker.
I guess you keep doing it
until we find the real one.
- Ouch.
- No offense.
- Okay.
- Okay. You got it.
Find Peter Parker.
- What's the thing on his hand?
- Shh.
Find Peter Parker.
Find Peter Parker!
Great, it's just
some random guy.
Hello.
Um, I hope it's okay,
I just came through this, uh...
Oh. It just closed.
You're Peter?
Yeah. Peter Parker.
I... I've seen you two...
Hi. Heh.
Wait. He's...
He's not your friend.
Huh.
Wait. So you're Spider-Man too?
Why didn't you just say that?
I generally don't
go around advertising it.
Kind of defeats the whole
anonymous superhero thing.
- I said that.
- That's what he just said.
My lola's asking if you could
clean up the webs you just shot.
- Oh, sorry, Lola.
- Yes, of course.
- I'm going to bed.
- Night, Lola.
Good night, Ned's lola.
Uh,
this might seem kind of weird,
but I've been trying
to find your friend
ever since I got here.
I just have this sense that...
That he needs my help.
Our help.
He does.
We don't know where he is.
And, um, honestly, right now
we're all he really has left.
Well, uh, is there someplace
that he might go
that has meaning to him?
Like a place
where he would go to just...?
Get away from everything?
For me, it was the top
of the Chrysler Building.
Empire State.
- It's a better view.
- That is a sweet view.
Yes.
Yeah. I... I think I know
exactly where that would be.
I'm sorry.
Peter, there's...
There's some people here.
- What?
- Um...
Hey, wait, wait! Whoa!
What...?
Sorry...
about May.
Yeah. Sorry.
I got some understanding
of what it is you're...
No, please don't tell me that
you know what I'm going through.
- Okay.
- She's gone.
And it's all my fault.
She died for nothing.
So I'm gonna do what I should
have done in the first place.
- Peter...
- Please don't.
You don't belong here.
Either of you.
So I'm sending you home.
Those other guys
are from your worlds, right?
So you deal with it.
If they die, if you kill them...
that's on you.
It's not my problem.
I don't care anymore.
I'm done.
I'm really sorry
that I dragged you into this.
But you have to go home now.
Good luck.
My Uncle Ben was killed.
It was my fault.
I lost...
I lost Gwen, my, um...
She was my MJ.
I couldn't save her.
I'm never gonna be able
to forgive myself for that.
But I carried on,
tried to, um...
Tried to keep going,
tried to keep being the, uh...
The friendly neighborhood
Spider-Man
'cause I know that's what
she would've wanted.
But at some point, I just...
I stopped pulling my punches.
I got rageful.
I got bitter.
I just don't want you
to end up like... Like me.
The night Ben died...
I hunted down the man
who I thought did it.
I wanted him dead.
I got what I wanted.
It didn't make it better.
It took me a long time...
to learn to get through
that darkness.
I wanna kill him.
I wanna tear him apart.
I can still hear
her voice in my head.
Even after she was hurt,
she said to me
that we did the right thing.
She told me
that with great power...
Comes great responsibility.
Wait, what?
How do you know that?
Uncle Ben said it.
The day he died.
Maybe she didn't die
for nothing, Peter.
Okay, so, uh, Connors,
Marko, Dillon and, um...
I think that I can repair the
devices for Dillon and Marko,
but the others...
Oh, I got Connors. I've cured
him once, so no big deal.
- What? It's no big deal.
- Great.
Yeah, that's great.
I think I can make
an anti-serum for Dr. Osborn.
Been thinking about it
a long time.
Gotta cure all of them. Right?
Right.
That's what we do.
What?
Just three yous.
Um...
So do you have
a best friend too?
I did.
You did?
He died in my arms...
after he tried to kill me.
It was heartbreaking.
Dude.
- Hey.
- Will you run a diagnostic?
Yeah.
Hey, you okay?
Uh, yeah, I'm fine.
Are you okay?
Mm-hm.
You don't deserve this.
- I've ruined your life.
- No. No, no, no.
Look at me. I'm here.
Not going anywhere.
We're gonna get through this.
And we're gonna get
through it together.
Okay?
Okay.
Thank you.
You have someone?
No.
Ah, I got no time for
Peter Parker stuff, you know?
Hm.
- Do you?
- Uh...
- that's a little complicated.
- Oh, I understand.
I guess it's just not
in the cards for guys like us.
Well, I wouldn't give up.
Took a while
but we made it work.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
Me and...
MJ.
My MJ. Uh...
It gets confusing here.
Yeah.
- Peter!
- Yeah?
- Oh, sorry, did you mean...?
- "Peter" Peter.
- We're all called Peter.
- We're all Peter.
- Peter Parker?
- Again, we're all Peter Parker.
- The computer.
- Oh!
- Oh, I'm ready.
- Yeah. Me too.
Okay, so now, all we gotta do
is lure these guys
someplace, right?
Try to cure them
while they try to kill us,
and then send them home.
- Using a magic box.
- Well, that's the plan.
Are you gonna go into battle
dressed as a cool youth pastor,
or do you got your suit?
- Good.
- Here's your web cartridges.
- Oh, thanks, man.
- What's that for?
Uh, it's my web fluid.
It's for my web shooters. Why?
Whoa!
That came out of you.
Yeah. You can't do that, huh?
- No.
- How on earth does that...?
We're getting sidetracked. This
is where we'll do this, okay?
It's isolated,
so no one should get hurt.
We draw them there with the box.
It's the thing they want.
All we have to do
is figure out how to get there.
- We could portal there.
- What?
- I'm magic now.
- Yeah, he's right. He can.
- Yeah, we saw.
- Yeah, he is.
- Wait, really?
- I got Doctor Strange magic.
- No way.
- Yeah.
I promise,
I won't turn into a supervillain
and try to kill you.
Okay.
Thank you.
Um, all right,
here goes nothing.
What's that thing
you always say?
- Expect disappointment and...
- No, no, no.
We're gonna kick some ass.
Okay.
Cure. Cure some ass.
Cure that ass.
Ladies and gentlemen,
the Bugle tip line
has just received a call
from none other than the
fugitive known as Spider-Man,
fresh from his rampage
in Queens.
So, Peter Parker,
what pernicious propaganda
are you peddling?
- Just the truth.
- Oh, sure.
The truth is...
that this is all my fault.
I accidentally brought
those dangerous people here.
Well, he admits it.
And if those people
are watching...
just know that I really did
try to help you.
I mean,
I could have killed you...
at any given moment,
but I didn't.
My Aunt May taught me
that everyone deserves
a second chance.
That's why I'm here.
And where is "here," exactly?
A place that represents
second chances.
The Statue of Liberty?
Good God, folks.
He's about to destroy
another national landmark.
World, if you're watching...
Believe me,
the world is watching.
...wish me luck.
Your friendly neighborhood
Spider-Man could use some.
Okay, guys,
it could be any minute now.
Yep, almost done.
You know, Max was like
the sweetest guy ever
before he fell into...
a pool of electric eels.
That'll do it.
Mm. Oh, there it goes.
Heh, you okay?
Oh, it's my back.
It's kind of stiff
from all the swinging, I guess.
Yeah. No, I got
a middle back thing too.
- Really?
- Yeah. You want me to crack it?
- Yeah.
- Yeah?
- Yeah, that'd be great.
- All right.
- You ready?
- Yeah.
Yep. That's good.
- How is it?
- Wow.
- That's good. That's better.
- Right? Yeah.
Wow.
This is so cool.
I always wanted brothers.
So you, like, make your own
web fluid in your body?
I'd rather not talk about this.
- I don't mean to...
- But are you teasing me?
No, no.
He's not teasing you.
It's just that we can't do that,
so we're curious as to how your
web situation works, that's all.
If it's personal, I don't wanna
pry, but I think it's cool.
I... I wish I could tell you,
but it's, like, I don't do it.
Like I don't...
Like I don't do breathing.
- Like, breathing just happens.
- Whoa.
Does it just come out
of your wrists,
or does it come out
of anywhere else?
Only... Only the wrists.
Never had a block?
I run out of webs all the time.
- I have to make my own in a lab.
- Right. That's...
It's a hassle compared
to what you got.
Sounds like a hassle.
But I did.
You said that, I was like,
- "Oh, I had a web block."
- Whoa. Why?
Existential crisis stuff.
Yeah.
Don't get me started on that.
Hey. What are, like,
some of the craziest villains
- that you guys have fought?
- Seems you've met some of them.
Heh-heh, that's a good question.
Yeah, I fought an alien
made out of black goo once.
Oh, no way.
I fought an alien too.
- On Earth and in space.
- Oh.
- He was purple.
- I wanna fight an alien.
I'm still, like, that you fought
an alien in space.
I'm lame compared...
I fought a Russian guy
in a rhinoceros machine.
Can we rewind it back
to the "I'm lame" part?
- 'Cause you are not.
- Thanks. I appreciate that.
- I'm not saying I am...
- But it's just the self-talk.
- Maybe we should...
- Listen, I...
'Cause you're amazing.
Just to take it in for a minute.
- Yeah, I can take it in.
- You... You are amazing.
- I can. Thank you.
- You are amazing.
- Will you say it?
- I needed to hear that.
Thank you.
All right, guys, focus up.
You feel that?
Yeah.
What's up, Peter?
How you like the new-new?
Look, you give it to me,
I'm gonna destroy it.
But I'll let you live.
Don't make me a murderer, Peter.
Okay, guys, here he comes.
Hey, Max, I missed you, man. Ho!
All right, MJ, heads up!
Got it! Close it.
Uh, Ned, it's not closing.
Yeah, I know.
- Why isn't it closing?
- I don't know.
- Did you close it before? No?
- I mean, I've opened some.
Max, Max, Max.
Can we talk for a second?
- Just you and me, just talk?
- Look who showed up.
- My old friend Spider-Man.
- I'm trying to save you.
- That's all I've ever wanted.
- You're not trying to save me.
- I am.
- You ain't even the shit no more.
- Oh...
- Don't worry about me.
I'll save myself.
- Burn up!
- Aah! Whoa!
Well, I got his attention.
Now what?
Okay, great.
Just FYI, lizard guy's here too.
Guys, comm check. Hello?
I need Max's cure.
Yeah. I'm on it.
I need the Lizard cure.
Uh, okay, okay.
Where's the box, Peter?
- Flint, we could help everyone.
- I don't care!
Sorry!
Gross!
Sad to tell you, Sandman,
nobody's going home.
What the hell
is going on out there?
I keep yelling at you, Peter 2!
- But I thought you were Peter 2.
- What? I'm not Peter 2.
Stop arguing, both of you!
Listen to Peter 1.
We're clearly
not very good at this.
I know, I know. We suck.
I don't know
how to work as a team.
- Me neither.
- I do. I've been in a team, okay?
I don't wanna brag, but I will.
I was in the Avengers.
- The Avengers?
- Yeah.
- That's great.
- Thank you.
What is that?
- You don't have the Avengers?
- Is that a band?
- Are you in a band?
- No, I'm not in a band.
The Avengers is
Earth's mightiest...
- How's this helping?
- It's not important.
All we gotta do is focus,
trust your tingle
and coordinate our attacks.
Yes. Okay.
- Let's pick one target.
- Right.
We take them off the board
one at a time.
- You got it. Peter 1, Peter 2.
- Peter 2.
- Peter 3.
- Let's do this. Ready?
- Wait, wait, wait!
I love you guys.
Thank you.
- All right, let's do this.
- Let's go.
Yes!
Okay, Spider-Mans.
Sandman's first.
I'm gonna lead him
inside the statue.
I'll meet you at the top.
- Come on!
- Hey!
- Hey, Dr. Connors.
- Hello, Peter.
- Peter 1!
- I got it!
Flint, we're trying to help you!
Guys, I'm at the top.
I need the cure!
I'm coming, I'm coming,
I'm coming.
Just wait your turn, doc!
I'll be right back.
It's okay, Flint.
We're gonna get you home.
You just stay right here.
How do we stop him?
I've never seen him
this powerful.
It's the arc reactor.
We gotta get it off him.
You're not gonna
take this from me.
That's not gonna work.
We gotta do this up close.
Peter 2, go right.
Peter 3, go left.
On me. Unh!
Yeah!
I'm trying to close it.
I can't help that it's not working.
It's fine. You'll do it again.
We'll keep trying.
- All right, we got this.
- Focus and close the portal.
Close it.
Oh, no. No, no, no.
And that is a lizard,
and we should go!
Run!
Come on! Come on, this way.
Quick, quick, quick!
Connors, stop!
Yeah.
Leave them. They're mine.
I don't need your help.
I got it just fine.
Dr. Octavius, no.
What are you doing?
Get it off of me.
There you go.
MJ!
Whoa.
- We gotta hide this thing.
- Oh, right.
- Nice, Ned!
- Oh, yeah!
Oh.
Where is he?
- No!
- Wait, wait, wait.
Before you do anything, Mister...
Doctor Strange, sir,
Peter's plan is working.
- What plan?
- He's curing them.
Dr. Connors?
Welcome back, sir.
Well, I'll be damned.
Did you just open a portal?
Yes... Yes, sir, I did.
Hmm.
Max?
- Don't worry. I'm all tapped out.
- Are you sure about that?
Back to being a nobody.
- You were never a nobody, Max.
- Yes, I was. Yes, I was.
You didn't see me.
Can I tell you something,
though?
Yeah.
You got a nice face.
You're just a kid.
- Ehh...
- You're from Queens.
You got that suit.
You help a lot of poor people.
I just thought
you was gonna be Black.
- Oh, man, I'm sorry.
- Oh, don't apologize.
There's gotta be a Black
Spider-Man somewhere out there.
Goddamn eels.
The power of the sun.
In the palm of your hand.
Peter?
Otto.
Oh, it's good to see you,
dear boy.
It's good to see you.
You're all grown up.
How are you?
Trying to do better.
- Strange, wait, we're so close.
- Skip it!
I've been dangling over
the Grand Canyon for 12 hours.
I know, I know, I know.
I, uh... Um... Uh...
I'm sorry about that, sir.
I mean...
- You went to the Grand Canyon?
- He could have used your help.
It's okay.
Uh, these are my new friends.
This is Peter Parker, Peter
Parker. Spider-Man, Spider-Man.
They're mes
from other universes.
- No, no, no.
- They're here to help.
He's the wizard
I told you about.
Look, I am really impressed
that you've managed to give them
all a second chance, kid.
But this has to end. Now.
Can the Spider-Man
come out to play?
Strange, no!
Are you okay?
Yeah.
I'm okay.
Are you okay?
Whoa!
Thank you, Mr. Cape, sir.
Ned?
- Ned!
- Hey!
- MJ!
- Peter?
- Ned!
- Peter!
Hey!
- Are you okay?
- We're okay!
Poor Peter.
Too weak to send me home to die.
No.
I just wanna kill you myself.
Attaboy.
She was there because of you.
I may have struck the blow,
but you...
Ha-ha, you are the one
that killed her.
Peter.
What have I done?
- It's you.
- You okay?
Uh, yeah, I'm good.
I've been stabbed before.
- Oh, good, good, good.
- Hey.
- Oh, man.
- Hey, nice catch.
Nice throw.
What? Is that happening,
or am I dying?
Yeah, that's happening.
That's real.
Are there people in the sky?
- I gotta go.
- Yeah. I got it. You okay?
What's happening?
They're coming through.
I can't stop them.
There's gotta be
something we could do.
Can't you just
cast the spell again?
The original way,
before I screwed it up.
We're too late for that.
They're here.
They're here because of you.
What if everyone
forgot who I was?
What?
They're coming
because of me, right?
Because I'm Peter Parker?
So cast a new spell.
But this time, make everyone
forget who Peter Parker is.
Make everyone forget...
- me.
- No.
- But it would work, right?
- Yeah, it would work.
But you gotta understand,
that would mean that everyone
who knows and loves you, we...
We'd have no memory of you.
It would be as though
you never existed.
I know.
Do it.
You better go and say your
goodbyes. You don't have long.
- Thank you, sir.
- Call me Stephen.
Thank you, Stephen.
Yeah. Still feels weird.
I'll see you around.
So long, kid.
Hey. Uh, I think this is it.
- I think you're about to go home.
- Okay.
- All right.
- Um, look, I, uh...
Thank you.
I just wanna... I want you to...
I wanna tell you that...
I don't know how to say this.
- Peter.
- I want you to know that I...
You know. It's what we do.
Yeah, it's what we do. Um...
Right, I gotta find Ned and MJ.
I, uh...
Thank you, thank you, thank you.
- I guess I'll see you.
- See you.
Bye.
- Oh...
- You're in so much pain, huh?
- I am.
- Yeah.
Oh, you're okay. Oh!
Yeah, you did.
So proud of you.
- Are you okay?
- Yeah, we're okay.
- Oh, my God, you're bleeding.
- I'm fine. I'm okay.
- You sure?
- I'm fine, I promise.
- Okay, okay.
- I promise.
Good.
Um, we should go, right?
Yeah. You're gonna forget
who I am.
- What?
- Forget who you are?
What are you talking about?
It's okay.
I'm gonna come and find you,
and I'll explain everything.
I'll make you remember me.
And it'll be like none of this
ever happened. Okay?
But what if that doesn't work?
What if that doesn't work?
What if we can't remember you?
I don't wanna do that.
- I don't wanna do that.
- I know. MJ, I know.
There's not something we can do?
We can't come up with a plan?
There's always
something we can do.
There's nothing we can do.
But it'll be okay.
You promise?
Yeah, I promise.
I'll come find you, okay?
I know you will.
- Okay.
You better.
If you don't,
I'll just figure it out.
I've done it before,
I can do it again.
I promise I'll fix this.
I really hate magic.
Yeah. Me too.
I love you.
- I love...
- Just wait.
Wait and tell me
when you see me again.
Sure.
I love you.
It's been a few
weeks since the fiasco
on the Statue of Liberty,
and Spider-Man's cultists
continue to contend that
the vile vigilante is a hero.
Well, if he were a hero,
he'd unmask himself
and tell us who he really is,
because only a coward
conceals his identity.
Only a coward hides
his true intentions.
Rest assured,
ladies and gentlemen,
this reporter will uncover
those intentions
come hell or high water.
Hi. My name is Peter Parker.
You don't know me, but I, uh...
Hi, my name is Peter Parker,
and you don't know me, but you...
Okay, come on.
- No way.
- Hard to believe, isn't it?
Hey.
One sec. Can I help you?
Hi. Um, my name
is Peter Parker, and I...
would like a coffee, please.
Okay, no problem, Peter Parker.
Doughnut for
my fellow Engineer.
Oh! Wait, what?
MIT, they're the Engineers.
The mascot.
Oh, right, right, right.
I should probably know that.
Look at you
with the school spirit.
Tell anybody, I will deny it.
Oh, okay.
Peter Parker? Peter Parker.
Your coffee.
- Right. Thank you.
- Mm-hm.
Um...
Are you excited for MIT?
Oh, uh, right. Yeah.
Uh, yeah. Actually,
I am excited, which is weird,
'cause I don't really
get excited about things.
I kind of expect disappointment.
'Cause then you'll never
actually be disappointed.
Right?
Uh...
yeah. Right.
I don't know, it kind of
feels different
this time for some reason.
Right. Um...
What I was...
You okay?
It doesn't really hurt anymore.
Is there anything else?
No.
Thank you.
No problem.
I'll, uh, see you around.
How'd you know her?
Through Spider-Man.
You?
Same.
I lost a good friend
a while back.
Felt like this.
It hurts 'cause they're gone
and then it hurts all over again
because you remember
what they stood for
and you wonder,
"Is all that gone too?"
No, it's not gone.
Everyone that she helped...
they'll keep it going.
You really think so?
I know it.
- Take care of yourself, okay?
- Yeah. Nice to meet you.
Rent is due on the
first of the month. Don't be late.
Four-three-Edward,
do you need an EMS assist?
Negative, Central.
We're gonna need a car tow.
♪ Three
That's the magic number ♪
♪ Yes, it is
It's the magic number ♪
♪ Somewhere in
This hip-hop soul community ♪
♪ Was born three
Mase, Dove and me ♪
♪ And that's
The magic number ♪
♪ What does it all mean? ♪
♪ Difficult preaching
Is Posdnuos' pleasure ♪
♪ Pleasure and preaching
Starts in the heart ♪
♪ Something that stimulates
My music in my measure ♪
♪ Measure in the music
Raised in three parts ♪
♪ Casually see
But don't do like the soul ♪
♪ 'Cause seein' and doin'
Are actions for monkeys ♪
♪ Doin' hip-hop hustle
No rock 'n' roll ♪
♪ Unless your name's Brewster
'Cause Brewster's a Punk ♪
♪ Parents let go 'cause
There's magic in the air ♪
♪ Criticizing rap
Shows you're out of order ♪
♪ Stop, look and listen
To the phrasin' Fred Astaires ♪
♪ And don't get offended while
Mase do-si-do's your daughter ♪
♪ A tricameral system
Is now set ♪
♪ Fly rhymes are stored
On a D.A.I.S.Y. production ♪
♪ It stands for "Da Inner Sound
Y'all" and y'all can bet ♪
♪ That the action's not a trick
But sho'nuff a function ♪
♪ Everybody wants to be
A deejay ♪
♪ Everybody wants
To be an emcee ♪
♪ But no more, no less ♪
♪ And you don't have to guess ♪
♪ De La Soul posse
Consists of three ♪
♪ And that's the magic number ♪
♪ This here piece of the pie
Is not dessert ♪
♪ But the course that we dine ♪
♪ And three out of
Every darn time ♪
♪ The effect is "Mmmm" when
A daisy grows in your mind ♪
♪ Showing true position
This here piece is ♪
♪ Kissin' the part of the pie
That's missin' ♪
♪ When that negative number
Fills up your casualty ♪
- ♪ Three ♪
- ♪ Maybe you can subtract it ♪
♪ You can call it
Your lucky partner ♪
♪ Maybe you can call it
Your adjective ♪
♪ But odd as it may be ♪
♪ Without my one and two
Where would there be ♪
♪ My three
Mase, Pos and Me? ♪
♪ And that's the magic number ♪
♪ What does it all mean? ♪
♪ Focus is formed
By flaunts of the soul ♪
♪ Souls who flaunt styles
Gain praises by pounds ♪
♪ Common are speakers
Who honor the scroll ♪
♪ Scroll written daily
Creates a new sound ♪
♪ Listeners listen
'Cause this here is wisdom ♪
♪ Wisdom of a speaker
A Dove and a plug ♪
♪ Set aside a legal substance
To feed 'em ♪
♪ For now get 'em high
Off this dialect drug ♪
♪ Time is a factor
So it's time to count ♪
♪ Count not
The negative actions of one ♪
♪ Speakers of soul
Say it's time to shout ♪
♪ Three forms of soul
To a positive sum ♪
♪ Dance to this fix
And flex every muscle ♪
♪ Space can be filled
If you rise like my lumber ♪
♪ Advance to the tune
But don't do the hustle ♪
♪ Shake, rattle, roll
To my magic number ♪
♪ Now you may
Try to subtract it ♪
♪ But it just won't go away ♪
♪ Three times one ♪
♪ What is it? ♪
♪ One time three times one ♪
♪ Three times one ♪
- ♪ What is it? ♪
- ♪ Three ♪
♪ That's a magic number ♪
Okay.
Okay, I think I got this.
You're saying that
this whole place here,
it's just tons of...
superpeople.
And he has been
saying it for hours.
All right, tell me again.
I'm sorry, I'm an idiot.
There was a billionaire,
he had a tin suit
and he could fly, right?
Okay, and there was
a really angry green man.
- Hulk.
And you thought Lethal
Protector was a shit name.
Yeah, because it is.
Now tell me again
about your purple alien
that loves stones.
'Cause I'll tell you what, man,
aliens do not love stones.
- Eddie, don't start.
- They don't.
Know what aliens love?
Eating brains.
Because that's what they do.
All right?
Señor, he made
my family disappear.
For five years.
Five years?
That's a long time.
Maybe I...
Maybe I should go to New York
and speak to this...
Spider-Man.
Eddie, we are drunk.
Let's go skinny-dip!
I don't think
we should skinny-dip.
You have to pay the bill.
What is happening? No!
No, we just got here!
No, not again!
And there he goes.
Without paying the bill,
no tips, nothing.
Don't cast that spell.
- It's too dangerous.
- Why?
We tampered with
the stability of space-time.
The multiverse is a concept
about which we know
frighteningly little.
Your desecration of reality...
will not go unpunished.
It was the only way.
But I never meant
for any of this to happen.
Wanda.
Well, I knew sooner or later
you'd show up.
I made mistakes,
and people were hurt.
I'm not here to talk
about Westview.
Then what are you here for?
We need your help.
With what?
What do you know
about the multiverse?
I'm sorry, Stephen.
I hope you understand...
the greatest threat...
to our universe...
is you.
Things just got out of hand.